Noah Malmed

Software Developer

I am a full stack developer with over 7 years experience. For the past two years I've been working mainly in web development (Angular and Rails), but I enjoy all different types of programming. I'm looking for a position where I design and build impactful and interesting software from the ground up.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer / September 2021 - Present

Scholastica / Chicago

- Full Stack developer working on a web app that services academic journal editors and authors as well as internal tooling
- Writing, collaborating and reviewing JS/Angular and Ruby on Rails code
- Contributing to <u>Pandoc</u>, an open source Haskell library for document conversion
- Collaborating with company stakeholders to create executable code specs for myself and other developers to work on
- Maintaining and adding features to our CI, using Docker and Github actions

Software Developer / May 2019 - July 2021

Fast Radius / Chicago

- Full Stack developer working on a web app that handled both an internal admin portal and a customer facing app
- Writing, pairing and reviewing JS/React code and Elixir Phoenix code
- Working with product managers, designers and developers to define specifications for work
- Led interviews sessions for new developers.

Mobile App Developer / January 2018 - March 2019

Zooniverse / Chicago

- Sole mobile developer for the Zooniverse Android and iOS React Native apps
- Handled all user outreach including bug reports and feature requests

Technical Consultant / January 2016 - January 2018

Solstice / Chicago

- Worked as an iOS and React Native developer on the Discover Credit Card app
- Engaged with clients by demoing features and internal projects

CONTACT

Tel: 847-987-9486 noah.malmed@gmail.com@

EDUCATION

B.S. in Computer Science University of Illinois, Champaign Urbana

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Github</u>

SKILLS

- •Ruby/Rails
- •Elixir/Phoenix
- JavaScript (React and Angular)
- Postgres/Sql
- Docker
- Github Actions
- •AWS S3
- •Heroku
- Haskell
- Object Oriented Programming
- Functional Programming